WHICH IS THE CURRENT LANGUAGE?
Current and default language is (English).
I've added this option, so that you have the ability to translate and use this skin in your language.

HOW TO TRANSLATE TO YOUR LANGUAGE?
Duplicate the en.inc file, rename it to match your language code if it doesn't exist already
(Ex: French -> fr.inc, German -> de.inc, etc)
And translate the right part of the [=] or the word that is right to the colon [:]
Leave the quotation marks intact and separate each section with a comma [,].

THIS IS IMPORTANT!
When you finish, don't forget to change your language in the settings (both Language and Locale) and refresh Rainmeter!